https://www.micross.com/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement MicrossPrivacy StatementPrivacy PolicyThank you for visiting our website www.micross.com and we hope you find the information you are looking for. We are dedicated to safeguarding and preserving your privacy when visiting our site or communicating electronically with us.This Privacy Policy, together with our Terms of Use, provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you provide to us or that we collect from you.Information We CollectIn operating our website, we may collect and process the following data about you:Details of your visits to our website and the resources that you accessInformation you provide by completing forms on our websiteInformation provided to us when you communicate with us for any reasonUse of CookiesOn occasion, we may gather information about your computer for our services and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our website.Such information will not identify you personally. This information is statistical in nature about our visitors and their use of our site and does not identify any personal details whatsoever.Similarly to the above, we may gather information about your general internet use by using a cookie file. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our website and the service that we provide to you.All computers have the ability to decline cookies. This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular parts of our website.Use of Your InformationThe information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you. In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:To provide you with information requested from us, relating to our products or services. To provide information on other products which we feel may be of interest to you, where you have consented to receive such informationTo meet our contractual commitments to youTo notify you about any changes to our website, such as improvements or service/product changes, that may affect our serviceIf you are an existing customer, we may contact you with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.If you are a new customer, we will only contact you only when you have provided consent and only by those means you provided consent for.Storing Your Personal DataData that is provided to us is stored on our secure servers.The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically and transmission of such data is therefore entirely at your own risk. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password so that you can access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.Disclosing Your InformationWhere applicable, we may disclose your personal information to any member of our group. This includes, where applicable, our subsidiaries, our holding company and its other subsidiaries.We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time so please review this policy regularly.GDPRMicross and its subsidiaries comply with GDPR. For more detailed information, click here.Die & WaferAdvanced InterconnectPackaging & AssemblyComponent ModificationElectrical TestEnvironmental TestProductsAbout UsContact UsCareersTerms & ConditionsShipping MethodsPrivacy StatementSitemapOur Mission:To support customers’ system-critical requirements through delivering hi-reliability microelectronic components & services on-time and to specification.Can’t find what you’re looking for?
© 2020 Micross - All rights reserved worldwide. Website and services by LUXSON ltd © 2020 - all rights reserved.
Privacy PolicyBy using this online service you accept the handling of any personal data in accordance with the Privacy Policy. To view our Privacy Policy click here.
